<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<docset xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude" lifecycle="supported" id="appliance.kiwi-9" path="kiwi-9">
  <name>KIWI Appliance Builder</name>
  <version>9</version>
  <descriptions treatment="append">
    <desc lang="en-us">
      <p>
        KIWI NG (Next Generation) is the command-line utility to build Linux
        system appliances. The documentation published here is written for the
        latest KIWI NG upstream version. The upstream version may be slightly
        ahead of the version shipped in the latest release of SUSE Linux
        Enterprise.
      </p>
      <p>
        Builds of the upstream version of KIWI NG for your OS version are
        <a href="https://download.opensuse.org/repositories/Virtualization:/Appliances:/Builder">available from OBS</a>.
        These builds are supported on a best-effort basis.
      </p>
      </desc>
    <desc lang="de-de">
        <p>
        KIWI NG (Nächste Generation) ist ein Kommandozeilenwerkzeug, mit dem sich
        Linux-System-Appliances erstellen lassen.
        Die hier veröffentlichte Dokumentation wurde für die neueste Version von
        KIWI NG erstellt.
        Diese Upstream-Version kann etwas anders funktionieren, als die Version,
        die in der aktuellen Version von SUSE Linux Enterprise enthalten ist.
      </p>
      <p>
        Builds der Upstream-Version von KIWI NG für Ihr Betriebssystem finden Sie
        <a href="https://download.opensuse.org/repositories/Virtualization:/Appliances:/Builder">im OBS</a>.
        Wir bemühen uns, diese Builds zu unterstützen.
      </p>
      </desc>
    <desc lang="es-es">
      <p>
        KIWI NG (Next Generation) es la utilidad de línea de comandos para crear
        dispositivos de sistema Linux.
        La documentación publicada aquí está escrita para la versión de nivel
        superior más reciente de KIWI NG.
        Esta versión puede funcionar de forma ligeramente diferente a la versión
        incluida en la versión más reciente de SUSE Linux Enterprise.
      </p>
      <p>
        Las compilaciones de la versión de nivel superior de KIWI NG para la
        versión de su sistema operativo están
        <a href="https://download.opensuse.org/repositories/Virtualization:/Appliances:/Builder">disponibles en OBS</a>.
        La asistencia para estas compilaciones se ofrece con una filosofía de
        mejor esfuerzo.
      </p>
    </desc>
    <desc lang="fr-fr">
      <p>
        KIWI NG (Next Generation) est l'utilitaire de ligne de
        commande qui permet de créer des applicatifs système Linux.
        La documentation publiée ici est destinée à la dernière version en
        amont de KIWI NG.
        Cette version en amont peut fonctionner légèrement différemment de
        celle livrée dans la dernière édition de SUSE Linux Enterprise.
      </p>
      <p>
        Les builds de la version en amont de KIWI NG pour votre version de
        système d'exploitation sont
        <a href="https://download.opensuse.org/repositories/Virtualization:/Appliances:/Builder">disponibles sur OBS</a>.
        Ces builds sont pris en charge du mieux possible.
      </p>
    </desc>
    <desc lang="ja-jp">
      <p>
        KIWI NG (Next Generation)は、Linuxシステムアプライアンスを構築するためのコマンドラインユーティリティです。ここで公開されているマニュアルは、最新のKIWI NGアップストリームバージョン用に作成されています。このアップストリームバージョンは、SUSE Linux Enterpriseの最新リリースで出荷されたバージョンとは若干異なる動作をする場合があります。
      </p>
      <p>
        ご使用のOSバージョン向けKIWI NGのアップストリームバージョンのビルドは、<a href="https://download.opensuse.org/repositories/Virtualization:/Appliances:/Builder">OBSから入手可能</a>です。これらのビルドは、ベストエフォートベースでサポートされています。
      </p>
    </desc>
    <desc lang="pt-br">
      <p>
        KIWI NG (Next Generation) é o utilitário de linha de comando para criar
        aplicações de sistema Linux.
        A documentação publicada aqui foi escrita para a versão de upstream
        mais recente do KIWI NG.
        Essa versão de upstream pode funcionar de maneira um pouco diferente da
        versão fornecida no último lançamento do SUSE Linux Enterprise.
      </p>
      <p>
        Os builds da versão de upstream do KIWI NG referentes à sua versão do OS estão
        <a href="https://download.opensuse.org/repositories/Virtualization:/Appliances:/Builder">disponíveis no OBS</a>.
        Esses builds são suportados na base dos melhores esforços.
      </p>
    </desc>
    <desc lang="zh-cn">
      <p>
        KIWI NG（下一代）是用于构建 Linux 系统设备的命令行实用程序。此处发布的文档是为最新的 KIWI NG 上游版本编写的。此上游版本的工作方式可能与最新的 SUSE Linux Enterprise 版本中随附的版本略有不同。
      </p>
      <p>
        适用于您的操作系统版本的 KIWI NG 上游版本的内部版本<a href="https://download.opensuse.org/repositories/Virtualization:/Appliances:/Builder">可从 OBS 获得</a>。我们会尽最大努力为这些内部版本提供支持。
      </p>
    </desc>
  </descriptions>
  <resources>
    <git remote="https://github.com/OSInside/kiwi-suse-doc.git"/>
    <locale lang="en-us" sitemap="false">
      <branch>master</branch>
      <subdir>doc/build</subdir>
      <deliverable id="app.kiwi-9.dc-kiwi" type="dc">
        <dc file="DC-kiwi">
          <format epub="0" html="1" pdf="1" single-html="1"/>
        </dc>
      </deliverable>
    </locale>
  </resources>
</docset>
